bgo.com 2014-02-27

# bgo Privacy Policy | Quick Note on Privacy at bgo

#### bgo.com Privacy Policy

Our Privacy Policy is perhaps one of the most important things that all of our players should read. It lets you know how Mandalay Gaming Holdings Ltd (the “Company”, herein referred to as “us” or “we”) handle the information and data that you give to us, both when you register and as you play, and what we use that data for. 

It is important to note that by registering an account with us, you agree to this policy and consent to the use of your data as provided to us for any and/or all means as detailed below. 

By registering, making financial transactions, browsing bgo.com (the “Website”) and playing in the game, you provide us with data which can be used for the means of marketing and to provide a better service to you. If you do not agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy please do not register an account with us, nor use the Website or otherwise provide us with your personal information. 

##### **What information do we collect?**

We collect all sorts of information about you, mainly to help provide you with a better service, but also for legal requirements. We collect the following from every player: 

  1. Your personal information, including but not limited to your full name, household address, contact telephone numbers, date of birth and email address when registering an account.
  2. Information on your visits to the Website, including but not limited to, your current location, system information and traffic history (see cookies). 
  3. Your responses to any survey that we may undertake, should you elect to take part.
  4. Full, detailed records on any transaction that you may process via the Website, telephone, chat session or email.
  5. Full, detailed records of any correspondence that you may have with us. This information can be collected from emails, chat transcripts, telephone calls or any other means by which you may contact us.

We collate all of this useful information and try to make your bgo experiences even better. Using your data, we do the following: 

  1. Help speed up the processing of your deposits & withdrawals
  2. Speed up your browser navigation by displaying your most popular options in a more prominent section of the website
  3. Improve the accuracy of your account information without having to contact you
  4. Manage your account more effectively whenever we need to help you
  5. Comply with our Alderney gaming license and regulatory responsibilities
  6. Build profiles of players and help improve our service as a whole
  7. Carry out targeted surveys and customer analysis
  8. Provide you with promotional offers we feel will suit you, provided additional consent is given
  9. Monitor transactions to help prevent fraudulent activity on the Website

##### **How we store your information**

We take security extremely seriously. We will endeavour to ensure that your personal information is stored as securely as possible, well within guidelines provided by the Data Protection Act and our gaming license. We only disclose information that we have collected about you to closely associated partners or subsidiaries of Mandalay Gaming holdings Ltd. No 3rd party of no relation to us will ever receive your data. Any business partners, successors to the bgo brand or suppliers whom we engage will be provided access to the stored information. 

To assist us in complying with our regulatory duties, we may disclose your personal information to credit reference agencies or a third party whom we feel necessary to view such information. For the purposes of Anti money laundering and the prevention of Fraud, references may be made to both legal authorities as well as financial institutions. Additional security checks may be required in some cases. 

##### **Telephone Calls**

Any telephone calls made to bgo.com are recorded for quality control and training purposes. These calls may not be accessed by staff members but may be used in the event of any dispute, if required by an arbitrating 3rd party. 

##### **Our Cookies Policy**

We use cookies on our Website and they are essential to the correct operation. We highly recommend all players read our Cookies Policy for more information on how we retrieve and use data from Cookies. 

##### **Internet References & Transfers**

Due to the nature of the Internet, some partners of Mandalay Gaming Holdings may be based outside of the European Economic Area (EEA). As a result of this, the transmission of your data and subsequent processing and checking may take place outside of the EEA. By registering an account with us, you agree to have such information passed to partners where applicable to undergo processing as deemed necessary by us. We take all reasonable steps to ensure that any information passed to these partners is done so securely and in accordance with our Privacy Policy. 

##### **Disclosure of your Information**

By registering an account with us you hereby agree that we are entitled to share any and all information that we may hold on you, including all transactional history, gameplay logs and personal information with any regulator, independent arbitrator and/or legal authority whom may request such information as we see fit. This information will be passed to such authorities for the purposes of Anti Money laundering investigations, Fraud investigations and/or any Sports integrity investigation. Sensitive financial data will **never** be disclosed to any of these without explicit legal consent from a court of law. 

To comply with current Data Protection laws as well as our obligations as a responsible operator, all information will be stored for a period not less than six years after the closure of an account. 

##### **Your Rights to your data**

You are fully entitled to request all of the information that we hold on you, in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998. Any request to view such information will be subject to an administration fee of £20 plus any additional security and/or postage costs. 

##### **Changes to this Privacy Policy**

From time to time we may make changes to this Privacy statement. This may be to comply with new laws or to help make our service better for you. Any updates will be posted on this page and will be effective from the moment of posting, unless otherwise stated. Any material information changes that may have a significant effect on your current use of the Website will be sent to you via your registered email address, or where possible, via notice on the Website. We are not obliged to ensure your receipt of such information, so we recommend that you periodically check this policy no less than once per month. 

##### **Direct Marketing**

Out of respect for your right to privacy we are happy to provide you with an easy means to decline receiving email offers from us. In order to unsubscribe from our emails, please click the ‘Unsubscribe link’ that can be found at the bottom of every email we send. Alternatively, you may request to discontinue receiving these offers by sending a blank message with the word "Remove" in the subject area to [support@bgo.com](mailto:support@bgo.com). 

##### **Information about us:**

BGO Entertainment Limited.  
Inchalla, Le Val, Alderney, GY9 3UL  
+44 1481 822795

__Back to Top

#### bgo.com Cookies Policy

bgo.com uses “cookies” to help make your experience on our website as good as it could possibly be. Cookies are simple text files that Internet browsers, such as Internet Explorer or Firefox use and they help us to give you a much more personalised service when using bgo.com. 

Each Cookie contains small amounts of information which are stored on your computer, mobile phone or whatever device you may be using to visit our site. Whenever you visit bgo.com, our website retrieves this cookie and it tells us what your preferences are. 

Search engine giant Google have made a great video which explains how cookies work and why they’re so beneficial for both you as a customer, and us as a service provider. You can watch the video here: www.google.co.uk/goodtoknow/data-on-the-web/cookies 

##### **How we use cookies**

We use cookies at bgo.com to deliver a better service to you. The ways in which we use them are: 

  1. To allow you to log in to your bgo.com user account and play our games
  2. To allow you to choose certain login preferences wherever available
  3. To monitor your activity when on the website, helping us improve our service to you
  4. To help protect against fraudulent activity

This is just a small sample of how cookies help us help you. There are more, but these are the important ones. 

Cookies are often essential to the operation of a website. This is true in our case – without them, you wouldn’t be able to log in or play in the games. Below is a full list of exactly how your cookies work with bgo.com and why they’re essential: 

**Session cookies** – We have to be able to monitor when you’re logged in. It’s the law. So these cookies are essential to allow you the use of the website. They also help manage your session information and let you navigate the different sections of the website. 

**Functionality & Preferences** – Your preferences are important to how we provide a better service to you, so our Functionality cookies store information based on your previous choices. They remember your choice of language on the site, which games you enjoy playing, when your last visit was, etc. They also help us recognise when you’ve been sent messages or what offers you may be entitled to. 

**Prevention of Fraud** – Sorry, we can’t go into much detail here, but rest assured our cookies are very clever and they help us detect fraudulent behaviour, thus protecting our real customers from any danger. 

**Traffic Management** – This one’s a bit boring, but nonetheless crucial to the way we operate the website. These traffic cookies help us track information about how players arrived at our website, meaning we can make better use our promotions and bring more players in. The more the merrier, right? 

It’s important to add that bgo.com uses tracking cookies from bgo Partners – our affiliate operator. The two businesses are directly related, so technically no 3rd party is involved, but they are ultimately 2 separate areas of our Business. 

Any links that you may see to bgo.com or other areas of our Website on other websites will most likely be using their own cookies, meaning we have no control over the information they are storing on your PC. Only bgo.com has access to the information stored in that particular cookie, so everything that we have previously mentioned is totally secure – no one will be able to view your preferences or personal details. 

##### **Manage your cookies**

If you’re not too sure about cookies then you have total control over whether or not you allow them to be stored on your system. We have to make a point that if you do not allow cookies to be stored on your system from bgo.com then you won’t be able to use our services. Sorry about that, but it’s an essential part of the system! 

You can clear your cookies in your Web Browsers system tools, as well as changing your privacy settings to allow or do not allow cookies in the future. We highly recommend that you set [bgo.com](https://www.bgo.com/) as Trusted Domain, meaning our website will be able to work without any hiccups at your side. 

We also recommend that you visit [allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/) if you have any more questions about cookies. 

We also recommend that you read our Privacy Policy to see how we keep your details safe and secure, but also how we use them to make your bgo experience even better. 

__Back to Top
